ILGWU International Relations Department Records 5780/062
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Jordan, 1992-1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Kenya, 1982-1995 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Korea, 1981-1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Korea, 1981-1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Korea, 1981-1994 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Lebanon, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Lesotho, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Liberia, 1983-1994 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Malawi, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Malaysia, 1980-1995 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Mauritius, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Malaysia Trades Union Congress, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Mexico, 1979-1995 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Mexico, 1979-1995 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Mexico, 1979-1995 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Morocco, 1980-1995 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Mozambique, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Namibia, 1980-1989 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Nepal, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Netherlands, 1979-1994 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- New Zealand, 1979-1994 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Nicaragua, 1989-1995 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Nicaragua, 1979-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Nicaragua, 1979-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Nigeria, 1983-1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Norway, 1979-1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Panama, 1980-1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Pakistan, 1988-1995 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Paraguay, 1986-1993 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Peru, 1987-1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Philippines, 1985-1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Philippines, 1985-1995 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Poland, 1981-1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Poland, 1981-1995 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Poland, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Portugal, 1981-1993 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Romania, 1989-1994 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Russia, 1992-1994 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Senegal, 1985-1995 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Singapore, 1992-1994 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Somalia, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- South Africa, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Spain, 1980-1994 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Sri Lanka, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Sudan, 1989-1993 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Surinam, 1983-1989 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Sweden, 1980-1995 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Taiwan, 1985-1994 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Tanzania, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Thailand, 1985-1996 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Thailand, 1985-1996 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Trinidad and Tobago, 1981-1995 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Tunisia, 1984-1995 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Turkey, 1985-1988 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Turkey, 1985-1998 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Uganda, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Ukraine, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- United Arab Emirates, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- United Kingdom, 1980-1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- U.S.S.R., 1980-1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- U.S.S.R., 1980-1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- United States of America, 1980-1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Uruguay, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Venezuela, 1979-1993 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Vietnam, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Yugoslavia/Bosnia, 1981-1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Zambia, 1983-1991 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Zaire/Congo, 1987-1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Zimbabwe, 1982-1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Freedom House, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Freedom House, 1993-1995 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- GATT/MFA (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade/Multi Fibre Arrangement), 1977-1994 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- GATT/MFA, 1977-1994 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- GATT/MFA, 1977-1994 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- General System of Preferences, 1989-1995 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- General Articles of Interest, 1988-1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Global Economy, 1990-1994 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Homework, 1984-1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Human and Trade Union Rights, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Immigration and Migrant Workers, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- International Institute for Labour Studies (Box 38, Folder 12)
- International Labor Solidarity, 1989-1992 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- International Organizing, General, 1992-1995 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- International Organizing, General, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- International Trade, General, 1982-1993 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- International Trade, General, 1982-1993 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- International Women's Day, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Leslie Fray, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Leslie Fray, 1992-1995 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Leslie Fray, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Levi-Strauss, 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Maidenform, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Maquiladora Plants, 1986-1994 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Maquiladora Plants, 1986-1994 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Multinationals, 1981-1994 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- NAFTA, 1990-1995 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- NAFTA, 1990-1995 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- NAFTA, 1990-1995 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Parental/Family Leave, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Phillips Van-Heusen Corp., 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Republican Party, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Sindicato Dei Cittadino, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Speedo, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Textile Negotiations and Workers Rights, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Third World Debt, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Third World Debt, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Toycott/Toy Industries, 1993-1995 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Toycott/Toy Industries, 1993-1995 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Trade and Workers' Rights, 1986-1995 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Trade and Workers' Rights, 1986-1995 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Transnational Corporations, 1976-1995 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Transnational Coporations, 1976-1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Transnational Corporations, 1976-1995 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Transnational Corporations, 1976-1995 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- United Nations, 1987-1995 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- United Nations, 1987-1995 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- U.S. Aid (U.S. Agency for International Development), 1992-1994 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- U.S. Department of Labor, 1984-1994 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- U.S. Department of State, 1980-1990 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- U.S. Economy, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- U.S. Garment and Textile Industries, 1983-1995 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- U.S. Garment and Textile Industries, 1983-1995 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- U.S. Legislation, New and Pending, 1990-1995 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- U.S. Prison Labor, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Used Clothing, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Wacoal Limited, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Warren Company, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Women and Trade Unions, 1986-1994 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Women and Trade Unions, 1986-1994 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Women and Trade Unions, 1986-1994 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Articles on American Labor, American Unions, 1979-1995 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Articles on American Labor, American Unions, 1979-1995 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Center for International Studies (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Child Labor, 1987-1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  1 of
- Child Labor, 1987-1995 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  2 of
- Child Labor, 1987-1995 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  3 of
- Child Labor, 1987-1995 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  4 of
- Child Labor, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Child Labor, United States, 1989-1995 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Clinton Administration/Democratic party, 1984-1995 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Codes of Conduct, 1992-1995 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Ditchley Foundation, 1989-1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Domsey, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Domsey, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Domsey, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Domsey, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- European Union, 1988-1993 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- European Union, 1988-1993 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- European Union, 1988-1993 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Factory Fires, 1991-1995 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Free Trade Zones, 1982-1994 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Women and Trade Unions, 1986-1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Women and Trade Unions, 1986-1995 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Women Workers, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Work Councils, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Workers' Rights, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Workers' Rights, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Workers' Rights, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- World Trade Organization (WTO), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- World Bank and International Monetary Fund (IMF), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 9)